laptoplogic.com 2008-06-04

# Privacy Policy - LaptopLogic.com

_Last Updated on January 18, 2005_

At Laptop Logic™ LLC, LaptopLogic.com, we are committed in protecting your privacy. The following privacy statement discloses the types of information we gather and how we use it. 

**Collecting your Information**  
Our intention in collecting personal information is to provide you with more interesting and more specialized content and services. We collect personally identifiable information only when you provide it to us, such as when you elect to register in our forum, when you participate in a survey or contest or when you submit comments or a user review. The personally identifiable information is limited to: 

  * First and last name 

  * Home or business address 

  * E-mail address 

  * Telephone number 

  * Age 

  * Gender 

Personal information collected by our website often is limited to e-mail address, name, country or location, but may include other information when needed to provide a service to you. Information posted in the user reviews, user comments, and public forums will be viewed by the public. 

**Use of Cookies**   
Your Internet browser has a feature called “cookies” which stores small amounts of data on your computer about your visit to our site. You do not need cookies turned on in order to visit our site. Cookies cannot be matched with any personally identifiable information about you unless you have specifically given us personally identifiable information. We do not track individuals' use of the site. 

To ensure we are publishing content readers’ need and want, we may elect to collect aggregated site-visitation statistics using cookies. Cookies are collected for a variety of reasons, including: determining which features our overall population prefers the most; to ensure only one unique user review is submitted per article (This ensures the accuracy that only one individual submits a legitimate user review); Cookies are also collected in the message forum so users can conveniently login without having to re-enter their login information; and to display the most appropriate advertising based on your interests and to keep count on return visits to our site. 

If you have questions regarding this statement, you should contact [info@laptoplogic.com](mailto:info@laptoplogic.com)

 **Use of IP address  
** IP addresses are only recorded to help administer our web site and to determine which content is most preferred by our readers. IP addresses are not matched with any personally identifiable information unless you have specifically given us personally identifiable information. 

**Use of your information**   
We use your personal information for the following primary purposes: 

  * To help us create content most relevant to you. 

  * To help us determine if any modifications need to be made to our website or content. 

**Online Advertising**  
Certain companies assist us deliver interactive on-line advertising such as banner ads. These companies may collect and use information about our readers to help us better understand the type of advertising that are most relevant and appealing to you. The information is aggregated so it is not identifiable to a specific individual.

 **Links to non LaptopLogic Websites**  
LaptopLogic.com may contain links to other Web sites. LaptopLogic.com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of those other Web sites. 

**Security of your Personal Information**   
LaptopLogic.com will use its best efforts to protect the security of your personal information and honor your choices for its intended use. Your personal information is never shared outside the company without your permission, except under conditions explained above. 

**Contact Information**   
We welcome your comments regarding this Statement of Privacy, please contact us at [info@laptoplogic.com](mailto:info@laptoplogic.com)
